Becker, Frank J.; Papers apap224
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1953-1964; 1974; 1; 15.04 cubic ft.
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Federal Power Commission, Department, 1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Federal Trade Commission, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Flight Engineer Dispute, 1961 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Flight Engineer Dispute, 1961 (Flat-file 3)
  - Football Tickets, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, 1963 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22-25)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, Cuba, 1963 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, Israel, 1963 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, 1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, Cuba, 1964 (Box 6 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - General Services Administration, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Government Operations Committee, Legislation, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Government Operations Committee, Legislation, 1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Hafner, Harold R., Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Health, Welfare, Education, Krebiozen, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - House Administration, Legislation, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - House Administration, Legislation, 1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Iceland, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Interior, Department, 1961-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, Legislation, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, Legislation, 1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - International Communism Briefing, 1961 October 07 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 1, 1960 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 2, 1961 September (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 3, 1959 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21-22)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 4, 1960 May 10 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 5, 1960 February (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 6, 1961 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 7, 1959-1960 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, Legislation, 1963 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Humane Treatment), Legislation, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, Legislation, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Jobs, A-H, 1963-1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Jobs, L-M, O-P, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Jobs, Pages, R-S, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Jobs, Summer, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Jobs, T, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Jobs, W, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, Legislation, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, Legislation, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Judiciary Committee, Legislation, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Judiciary Committee, Legislation, 1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Judiciary Committee, Legislation, Civil Rights, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15-21)
  - Justice, Department, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Justice, Department, Immigration and Naturalization, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Labor, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Labor, Legislation, 1963 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Labor, Legislation, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Legislation, General Correspondence about 88th Congress, 1963 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - Legislation, General Correspondence about 88th Congress, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Materials about Thaddeus Kosciusczko and 4H Clubs, 1961 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Marine Corps, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, Legislation, 1963 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, Legislation, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Monroe Doctrine, Petition of Preservation, 1963 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Nassau County, Bellmore Training Center, Army, 1957 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Nassau County, Bellmore Training Center, Army, 1957-1958 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Adm., Department, 1961-1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14-15)
  - National Science Foundation, Department, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Navy, Contracts, Joseph A. Boga, 1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Navy, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18-19)
  - Navy, New York Naval Shipyard, 1963-1964 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1954 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21-22)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1955 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1956 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1957 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1958 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1959 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1960 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1961-1962 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, General, 1961-1962 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Newsletter, 1961 February (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, Booklets Sent to Enclosed, No Letter, 1961 February (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 February (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5-11)
  - Newsletter, 1961 November 08 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 November 08 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Newsletter, 1961 November 30 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 November 30 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Newsletter, 1961 December 10 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 December 10 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Newsletter, 1961 December 21 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 December 21 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Newsletter, 1962 January 31 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 January 31 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Newsletter, 1962 February 13 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 February 13 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Newsletter, 1962 April 17 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 April 17 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Newsletter, 1962 April 20 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 April 20 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Newsletter, 1962 September 17 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 September 17 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Newsletter, 1962 October 04 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 October 04 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Newsday Letter, 1963 August (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Newsletter, Washington Report, 1963 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1953-1954 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1955 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1955 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1956 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1956 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1957 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1957 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1958 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1958 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1959 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - News Releases, General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1959 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1960 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1960 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9-10)
  - News Releases, 1961 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1961 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - News Releases, Washington Reports, 1961 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - News Releases, 1962 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - News Releases, 1963 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - News Releases, Long Island Newspapers, 1963 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - News Releases, 1964 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Oral History Interview with Frank J. Becker, 1974 March 17 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Panama Canal, Dept., 1964 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Peace Corps, 1964 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Personal Affairs Institute, 1962 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Post Office, Department, 1962-1964 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23-24)
  - Post Office, Fifth District, 1963 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Post Office, Legislation, 1963 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Post Office, Legislation, 1964 (Box 11 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Post Office Cases, Atlantic Beach, 1953; 1956-1958; 1960-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Post Office Cases, Baldwin, 1955; 1957; 1960-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Post Office Cases, Bellmore, 1955; 1960-1962 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Post Office Cases, East Rockaway, 1961-1962 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Post Office Cases, Freeport, 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Post Office Cases, Hewlett, 1962-1964 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Post Office Cases, Island Park, 1960; 1962 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Post Office Cases, Lawrence, 1957-1960; 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Post Office Cases, Lido Beach, 1958; 1961-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Post Office Cases, Long Beach, 1964 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Post Office Cases, Malverne, 1959-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Post Office Cases, Merrick, 1961-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Post Office Cases, Nassau County, General, 1961-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Post Office Cases, Nassau County, General, 1963-1964 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Post Office Cases, North Merrick, 1953; 1955-1957; 1960-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Post Office Cases, Obscene Mail, 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Post Office Cases, Oceanside, 1953-1954; 1957-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Post Office Cases, Rockville Centre, 1961; 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Post Office Cases, Roosevelt, 1962 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Post Office Cases, Valley Stream, 1956-1964 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Post Office Cases, Wantagh, 1955-1957; 1959; 1961 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Post Office Cases, Woodmere, 1962-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Post Office Cases, Woodmere/Valley Stream, 1957-1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Prayer Amendment, 1963-1964 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Presidential Messages, 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Public Works, Jones and Rockaway Inlet, 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Public Works, Legislation, 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Public Works, Legislation, 1964 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Questionnaire, Army Reserve, Undated (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Questionnaire, Frank J. Becker, 1962 April (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Reports, 1960 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Reports, 1959-1960; 1962 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Republic Aviation Briefing, 1963 (Box 12 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Requests, A, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Requests, Agriculture Yearbook, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Requests, Agriculture Yearbook, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Requests, B, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Requests, C, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Requests, Calendars, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Requests, Celodyne Corporations, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Requests, D, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Requests, E, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Requests, F, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Requests, G, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Requests, H, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Requests, I, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Requests, Intern Programs, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Requests, J, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Requests, K, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Requests, L, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Requests, M, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Requests, N, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Requests, O, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Requests, P, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Requests, Publications, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22-23)
  - Requests, Q, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Requests, R, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Requests, S, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Requests, T, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Requests, V, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Requests, W, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Requests, Warren Commission Reports, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Requests, Z, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Rules, Legislation, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Rules, Legislation, 1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Science and Aeronautics, Legislation, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, Department, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Selective Service System, Department, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Small Business Administration, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Small Business Administration, Legislation, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Social Security, Al Levine, 1963 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Social Security, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40-41)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1955 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1956 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1957 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1958 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1959 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1960 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1961 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1962 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Speeches, Extra, Free Enterprise vs. The Welfare State, 1962 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1963 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State, Department, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - State, Department, Agency of International Development, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - State, Department, Passports, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Statements, Frank J. Becker, 1961 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Statements, Frank J. Becker, 1962 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Tariff Commission, Department, 1963 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Treasury, Department, 1962-1964 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Trips, Fort Dix, Undated (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Un-American Activities, Legislation, 1963 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - United Nations, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Veterans Administration, Department, 1963 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Veterans Affairs, Legislation, 1963 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Veterans Affairs, Legislation, 1964 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Veterans Committee, Letters, Discharge Petitions, 1963 (Box 14 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Visitors, 1963 January-1963 June (Box 15 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Visitors, 1963 July-1963 December (Box 15 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Visitors, 1964 January-1964 June (Box 15 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Washington Report, 1961 (Box 15 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Washington Report, 1962 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Washington Report, 1963 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Washington Report, 1964 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Waterways, 1953-1957 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, 1963 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, 1964 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Medical Care, 1963 (Box 16 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Medical Care, 1964 (Box 17 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Social Security, 1963 (Box 17 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Tariffs, 1963 (Box 17 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Tax, Frank J. Becker Speech, 1963 (Box 17 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - White House, 1963-1964 (Box 17 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - White House, President Kennedy's Assassination, 1963-1964 (Box 17 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1953-1964; 2; 2.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondence type.
  As a Congressman, Frank Becker interacted with his constituents continually, the most common method being through correspondence. The series documents three specific groups of individuals that Becker corresponded with: Immigrants (stamped IC on the paperwork), Servicemen (stamped SM on the paperwork), and Veterans (stamped VC on the paperwork). These are only a few of many groups of people Becker interacted with. However, Becker elected to keep this correspondence separate and the archivists maintained this order. Additionally, interspersed throughout the series are copies of original public laws, a questionnaire, and newspaper clippings.
  - Immigration, A, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, A, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Immigration, A, 1957 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Immigration, A, 1958 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Immigration, A, 1959 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Immigration, A, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Immigration, A, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Immigration, A, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Immigration, A, 1963 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Immigration, Allison, Calvin, Carmen, 1955-1958 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Immigration, B - [RESTRICTED], 1953-1954 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Immigration, B, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Immigration, B, 1957 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Immigration, B, 1958 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Immigration, B, 1959 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Immigration, B, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Immigration, B, 1961 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Immigration, B, 1962 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Immigration, B, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Immigration, Bedard, A., 1955 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Immigration, C, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Immigration, C, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Immigration, C, 1957 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Immigration, C, 1958 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Immigration, C, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, C, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Immigration, C, 1960-1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Immigration, C, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Immigration, C, 1961-1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Immigration, C, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Immigration, D, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Immigration, D, 1955-1959 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Immigration, D, 1956 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Immigration, D, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Immigration, D, 1957-1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Immigration, D, 1960-1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Immigration, D, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Immigration, D, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Immigration, E, 1953 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Immigration, E, 1955-1956 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Immigration, E, 1957 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Immigration, E, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Immigration, E, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Immigration, E, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Immigration, E, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Immigration, F, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Immigration, F, 1955-1956 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)